<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-02-06T21:01:48+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title>Tobey's chit chat</title><subtitle>This is apa915436's personal blog.</subtitle><entry><title>Chef Introduction</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/01/19/chef-introduction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chef Introduction" /><published>2017-01-19T03:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2017-01-19T03:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/19/chef-introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2017/01/19/chef-introduction/">&lt;p&gt;The topic of our 3rd week DevOps study group is Chef, a tool which automates and manages infrasture as code. The material is as below, as for the hands-on workshop, make sure to install vagrant and download chef server and client in advance to save time.'&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;//slides.com/apa915436/chef/embed&quot; width=&quot;576&quot; height=&quot;420&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Tobey</name></author><summary>The topic of our 3rd week DevOps study group is Chef, a tool which automates and manages infrasture as code. The material is as below, as for the hands-on workshop, make sure to install vagrant and download chef server and client in advance to save time.'</summary></entry><entry><title>CodePath x Girls in Tech Android Bootcamp</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/12/17/codepath-android-bootcamp/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CodePath x Girls in Tech Android Bootcamp" /><published>2016-12-17T02:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2016-12-17T02:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/17/codepath-android-bootcamp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2016/12/17/codepath-android-bootcamp/">&lt;p&gt;CodePath partners with Girls in Tech Taiwan to provide an 8-week accelerated android program. I volunteered to be one of the organizer. Here is my material for seconde week, the topic I'm gonna talk about is user interaction and flows, which will cover some simple concepts of action bars, snack bar, toast, event listners and intents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;//slides.com/apa915436/deck/embed?style=dark&quot; width=&quot;576&quot; height=&quot;420&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bootcamp link: &lt;a href=&quot;http://codepath.com/courses/girlsintechtw&quot;&gt;http://codepath.com/courses/girlsintechtw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Tobey</name></author><summary>CodePath partners with Girls in Tech Taiwan to provide an 8-week accelerated android program. I volunteered to be one of the organizer. Here is my material for seconde week, the topic I'm gonna talk about is user interaction and flows, which will cover some simple concepts of action bars, snack bar, toast, event listners and intents.</summary></entry><entry><title>Sweden society</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/18/sweden-society/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sweden society" /><published>2014-08-18T19:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2014-08-18T19:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/08/18/sweden-society</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/18/sweden-society/">&lt;p&gt;It’s been two weeks since I settled down here in Uppsala, Sweden. Something I’d like to tell more about would be freedom, equality and tolerance in this country. This might be a land free of discrimination, but just upon my observation. In Europe, it’s not a new thing that people scream at you in public occasions, trying to scare you off. For no other reason, just because you’re asian. This kind of stuff happens rarely in Sweden, at least it never happens to me. If yes, that would be little kids stunned seeing you with different hair color and exotic looking. That’s it! Swedish people just regard you as a human, a human that should be respected and shares all the rights mankind is supposed to have, no matter where you’re from, what color of your skin is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing Swedish people really surprise me is their care for the poor or say, their care for all mankind. Walking along the streets, you could probably see lots of homeless people, most are Gypsies as you could tell from their appearances, begging for money. Sweden, as a peaceful and tolerant country, accepts refugees from all over the world and even gives them permanent residency. There’s no other reason why they’re doing this, it’s because of their belief that everyone should be granted the rights of living. Often you can see people asking the homeless if they need help, giving them food, talking to them without labeling them as lazy or annoying. They just talk like they’re talking to a normal one instead of a homeless. It’s hard to describe how I felt when I saw this. Unless you see this happening in front of you, you could realize how strong the feeling is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last one I love the most about Sweden is equality on career. In Taiwan, my home country, people have stereotypes on different professions. For instance, if you’re a lawyer or a doctor, people admire you and respect you more since you have higher social status and, of course, more money. In Sweden, different occupations make no differences. I heard my Swedish teacher, a professor in the university, talking about her husband who works as a window cleaner. She said it without any hesitation or shame. This might not be the case in Taiwan though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;All occupations are considered of equal value&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This works in practice here in Sweden, not just a slogan.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Tobey</name></author><summary>It’s been two weeks since I settled down here in Uppsala, Sweden. Something I’d like to tell more about would be freedom, equality and tolerance in this country. This might be a land free of discrimination, but just upon my observation. In Europe, it’s not a new thing that people scream at you in public occasions, trying to scare you off. For no other reason, just because you’re asian. This kind of stuff happens rarely in Sweden, at least it never happens to me. If yes, that would be little kids stunned seeing you with different hair color and exotic looking. That’s it! Swedish people just regard you as a human, a human that should be respected and shares all the rights mankind is supposed to have, no matter where you’re from, what color of your skin is.</summary></entry></feed>
